<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="day">Day %d</string>
    <string name="appTheme">Learn a language regularly</string>

    <string name="title1">Go through all the letters</string>
    <string name="title2">Review grammar</string>
    <string name="title3">Organize your workspace</string>
    <string name="title4">Write about how your day went</string>
    <string name="title5">Look up new words in a dictionary</string>
    <string name="title6">Try teaching someone</string>
    <string name="title7">Read a chapter of a book</string>
    <string name="title8">Do 10 exercises</string>
    <string name="title9">Read news in your target language</string>
    <string name="title10">Learn about the culture of the language’s country</string>
    <string name="title11">Take an online walk</string>
    <string name="title12">Study vocabulary related to family</string>
    <string name="title13">Watch a video about the symbols of the country of your language</string>
    <string name="title14">Read a children’s book</string>
    <string name="title15">Spend time planning a trip</string>
    <string name="title16">Go to a library</string>
    <string name="title17">Describe your surroundings in the language you’re learning</string>
    <string name="title18">Learn vocabulary about your hobby</string>
    <string name="title19">Find an online friend</string>
    <string name="title20">Study with a tutor</string>
    <string name="title21">Tell something</string>
    <string name="title22">Download a language learning app</string>
    <string name="title23">Expand your vocabulary</string>
    <string name="title24">Focus on spoken language</string>
    <string name="title25">Learn how country names sound in your target language</string>
    <string name="title26">Learn the history of words</string>
    <string name="title27">Have a conversation with someone</string>
    <string name="title28">Watch your favorite movie in your target language</string>
    <string name="title29">Don’t doubt yourself</string>
    <string name="title30">Remember that mistakes are normal</string>

    <string name="desc1">Think about whether you have learned all the letters of the alphabet of the language you are studying. Do you remember how they are written and how to pronounce them? Many learners misunderstand which sound a certain letter is responsible for.</string>
    <string name="desc2">Review some grammar rules of the language. The more you repeat something, the longer you remember it. You might also see the rule from a different angle and understand it better.</string>
    <string name="desc3">Clean up your desk. Mess distracts you and makes studying uncomfortable.</string>
    <string name="desc4">Describe your day in the language you are learning. This way you will learn how everyday things are called. You will seriously expand your vocabulary with words that are actually useful in conversations.</string>
    <string name="desc5">Do you often see certain words but are not sure what they mean? Look them up in a dictionary. Otherwise your understanding of these words might be wrong.</string>
    <string name="desc6">Try giving a lesson in the language you are studying. To explain something to someone else, you have to truly understand it yourself. This will show you where you are strong and where you need to improve.</string>
    <string name="desc7">Read just one chapter of a book in the language you are learning. Step by step you will finish the whole book, learn many new words and rules, and most importantly understand how they are used in context.</string>
    <string name="desc8">Sometimes it is hard to make yourself study. Try doing just 10 simple exercises. You might get into it and suddenly realize you have been studying for an hour. And if not, you still did something. What matters is not how much you did, but that you did something at all.</string>
    <string name="desc9">Reading news in your target language can really help. News covers many different topics, and you will also stay aware of what is happening.</string>
    <string name="desc10">Culture and language are strongly connected. They directly influence each other. Knowing the culture helps you understand how native speakers think.</string>
    <string name="desc11">Open street view in a map app. You will learn more about the country where your target language is spoken, see signs, buildings, people, and understand the culture better.</string>
    <string name="desc12">Family is one of the basic topics in communication. If you know it well, it will be much easier to understand different kinds of materials.</string>
    <string name="desc13">A country’s symbol is the result of its cultural development. By learning the history of symbols, you can discover many new things - from the country’s history to the history of individual words.</string>
    <string name="desc14">Starting to learn a language is hard. Speech often contains complex and rare words that can slow you down. Start with children’s books. They contain many basic words that will give you a strong start.</string>
    <string name="desc15">If you are learning a foreign language, there is a good chance you want to visit the country where it is spoken. Start planning your trip now. This way you move closer to your goal instead of just thinking about it.</string>
    <string name="desc16">Libraries have all kinds of books. Find one you like and start studying right there. This kind of environment positively affects your concentration.</string>
    <string name="desc17">Movies and books contain many useful words. But they rarely include words you use at home. For example, the names of cutlery or furniture do not appear often. Without these words, it will be hard to hold a conversation.</string>
    <string name="desc18">Do you like your hobby? Do you want to get better at it? If yes, learning related vocabulary can seriously help. Knowing the right terms allows you to search for new ideas in another language environment and bring fresh ideas into your hobby.</string>
    <string name="desc19">To truly learn a language, it is not enough to read, write and listen. You also need to speak. Find a native speaker friend and talk to them. Nothing helps as much as immersion.</string>
    <string name="desc20">Self-study is very useful. But you cannot see yourself from the outside. A tutor can point out your mistakes and help you fix them.</string>
    <string name="desc21">Do you have a favorite story? Tell it to someone in the language you are learning. Any speaking practice is useful. Even if you are telling it to yourself.</string>
    <string name="desc22">Your phone is always with you. Download a language learning app. This way you can learn something new anytime.</string>
    <string name="desc23">Regularly learning new words is important. Do not neglect it.</string>
    <string name="desc24">Knowing many words does not mean they will help you in real conversations. You need to know spoken language so you do not sound like a textbook character.</string>
    <string name="desc25">Many countries have different names in different languages. Knowing them will help you understand the language better.</string>
    <string name="desc26">Many words have interesting origins. Knowing their history helps you remember them better and understand word formation and the logic of the language as a whole.</string>
    <string name="desc27">Conversation is very important. It trains your brain to react in fast-changing situations. This is how you build real speaking skills.</string>
    <string name="desc28">Watching your favorite movie in a foreign language is a powerful tool, especially if you have seen it in your native language. You already know what is happening and what the characters are saying. This helps you match foreign words with their meaning.</string>
    <string name="desc29">Learning a language is a difficult task. Do not doubt your abilities if you cannot understand something right away. Everything has its time.</string>
    <string name="desc30">Mistakes are part of the process. They are part of being human. Do not blame yourself for them. Learn from them and keep going.</string>
</resources>